ILR School Alumni Association Files /4083
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Alumni Association Files
1953-2009
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
/4083
3 cubic feet
3 linear ft.
Records (documents).
3086107
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, January 13, 2016
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 01, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3066: ILR School Alumni News /4118 MB: ILR School Alumni Memorabilia /4120: ILR School Alumni Scrapbooks /4130 AV: ILR School Alumni Weekend Audio-Visual Materials /4130 MB: ILR School Alumni Weekend "Reunion" Book Memorabilia /4289 PUBS: ILR School Alumni Affairs and Development Publications /4289 P: ILR School Alumni Affairs and Development Photographs 5542 AV: ILR School Alumni Seminar on Collective Bargaining in Sports Audio recordings
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Alumni Association.
3086107
- Files. (Box 1)
  - ILR Miscellaneous Material, 1953-1955 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Advisory Council - ILR, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Founders Project, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1975 Groat (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Brian Hartstein, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Board of Directors Election Ballots, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Board of Directors Biographies [folder 1 of 2], 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Board of Directors Biographies [folder 2 of 2], 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- ILRAA Board Members, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Board of Directors Election, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Board of Directors Election, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Board of Directors Election, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Board of Directors Election, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Board of Directors Election, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Palo Alto, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Board Member Materials, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Board of Directors Election Ballots, 2008-2009 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Board of Directors Election, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Board of Directors Election, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Board of Directors Election Ballots, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Board of Directors Election, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Board of Directors Election Ballots, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Board of Directors Election Ballots: Undeliverable, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  Scope and Contents
  Returned mail
- Board of Directors Biographies, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Board of Directors Election, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Board of Directors Election, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Board of Directors Election Ballots, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Board of Directors Election, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Board of Directors Members Materials Binder, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  Originals
- Board of Directors Miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Association History (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Cornell Songs (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Cornell Centennial Class Reunions, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Labor Programs, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- 60th Anniversary Labor Dinner, NYC, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  November 20077.
- ILR Campaign Committee (Box 3, Folder 13)
  Working Together
- ILR Employment and Disability Institute, 2000-2005 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Reflections on Progress at Work: Celebrating 50 Years, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- ILR Alumni News, 1991-1996 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Publicity: Lawler Interview, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Publicity: M.P.S., 1999 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Publicity: Press Releases, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- The ILR School at Fifty, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Hale-Bopp Comet and McGraw Tower, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- ILR Photograph (Box 3, Folder 22)
  Donald Moore, Robert McKersie, John McConnell